Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Local 649 Records, 1994-1998, IV.; 1 box
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, Financial Records, and Wage Scale Increase Request, August 27, 1997, 6 leaves (Box 36, Item 3252)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, and Financial Records, November 19, 1997, 7 leaves (Box 36, Item 3253)
  - Bulletin and Board Meeting, April 22, 1998, 2 leaves (Box 36, Item 3254)
  - Bulletin, August 26, 1998, 1 leaf (Box 36, Item 3255)
  - Board Meeting and Financial Records, September 9, 1998, 2 leaves (Box 36, Item 3256)
  - Board Meeting and Letter to Local 106-209 on Merger, October 17, 1998, 2 leaves (Box 36, Item 3257)
  - General Membership Meeting and Financial Records, October 18, 1998, 4 leaves (Box 36, Item 3258)
  - General Membership Meeting and Letter on Merger, November 18, 1998, 4 leaves (Box 36, Item 3259)
  - Marine Midland Checking Statements, December 12, 1997-November 13, 1998, 11 leaves (Box 36, Item 3260)
  - Marine Midland Canceled Checks and Ledger, 199?, 27 checks, 14 deposit receipts, 1 letter regarding lost checks, 1 ledger (Box 36, Item 3261)
  - Marine Midland Savings Statements, January 1, 1998-September 30, 1998, 4 leaves (Box 36, Item 3262)
  - Labor Organization Papers, 1989-1994, 13 leaves (Box 36, Item 3263)
  - Applications, July 6, 1998-July 21, 1998, 4 leaves (Box 36, Item 3264)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1991-1998, 14 leaves (Box 36, Item 3265)
- American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada Records, 1949-1995, V.; 1 box
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1949-1995, V.A; 1 box
    - 1949, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3266)
    - 1950, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3267)
    - 1953, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3268)
    - 1955, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3269)
    - 1956, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3270)
    - 1957, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3271)
    - 1958, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3272)
    - 1959, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3273)
    - 1961, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3274)
    - 1962, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3275)
    - 1965, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3276)
    - 1967, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3277)
    - 1968, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3278)
    - 1970, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3279)
    - 1971, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3280)
    - 1972, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3281)
    - Local 66, Rochester Musicians' Association By-Laws 1995, 1 booklet (Box 37, Item 3282)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Contributors
National League of Musicians. Local 23 (Buffalo, N.Y.); American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada. Local 43 (Buffalo, N.Y.); Colored Musicians Union of Buffalo (Buffalo, N.Y.); American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada. Hamburg Musicians' Association, Local 649 (Hamburg, N.Y.); American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada
Subjects
Labor unions--New York (State)--Buffalo; Musicians--Labor unions--New York (State)--Buffalo; Musicians--Salaries, etc.--New York (State)--Buffalo; Wages--New York (State)--Buffalo; Buffalo (N.Y.)--Labor unions; Buffalo Musicians' Association (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Archives
Genres
Administrative records; Correspondence; Professional directories; Financial records